<resources>
    <string name="title">How secure is my password?</string>
    <string name="about_message">2019 © Arctosoft AB\nVersion 1.8</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy policy</string>

    <string name="input">Input password:</string>
    <string name="info">About</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>

    <string name="pwd_title">Password generator</string>
    <string name="pwd_message">Drag the slider to select a password length and click generate</string>
    <string name="pwd_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="pwd_generate">Generate</string>
    <string name="pwd_notice_bad">Passwords that are less than 8 characters long are not recommended!</string>
    <string name="pwd_notice_good">Passwords that are more than 15 characters long are secure!</string>
    <string name="pwd_copied">Password copied to clipboard.</string>

    <string name="cb_showadvanced">Show advanced options</string>
    <string name="cb_lowercase">Lower case letters (\"a b c\")</string>
    <string name="cb_uppercase">Upper case letters (\"A B C\")</string>
    <string name="cb_numbers">Numbers (\"1 2 3\")</string>
    <string name="cb_specialchar">Special characters (\"# % @ &amp; .\")</string>

    <string name="password_tips">Password tips</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="generator">Generator</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="license">License</string>
    <string name="script_license">Script license</string>

    <string name="back_button_message">Press the back button again to exit!</string>

    <string name="generator_shortcut_long_label">Password Generator</string>
    <string name="generator_shortcut_short_label">Generator</string>

    <string name="generator_chars">%1$d/%2$d characters</string>

    <string name="info_message">The data and information in this app is purely for educational purposes and does not reflect real world situations.
    \n\nThe time-to-crack is based on 10 billion calculations per second (10GHz).
    \n\nPasswords are never stored or sent over the internet. All calculations are done locally on your device.
    </string>

    <string name="tips_message"><b>Here are some tips on how to create a strong password that\'s difficult to crack:</b>\n\n
        - Your password should be at least 8 characters long. (16+ is recommended)\n\n
    - Your password should contain lower case letters (\"a b c\"), \nupper case letters (\"A B C\"), \nnumbers (\"1 2 3\") and
        \nspecial characters (\". % &amp; @\")
    \n\n- Never use the exact same password on multiple accounts/websites. If one gets hacked, all the others may be in danger.
    \n\n- Your password shouldn\'t contain words, phone numbers or other things that are associated with you, since it makes
        guessing your password easier.
    \n\n- Replacing letters with numbers (e.g. the word \"Password\" to \"P455w0rd\") does not make a password more secure. The time it takes to crack
    it is almost the same.</string>

    <string name="license_script"><b>The following license applies to the script used to check the strength of passwords:</b>
    \n\nThe MIT License (MIT)Copyright &#169; 2015, Mark Nicholas Wales / Small Hadron Collider

    \n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to
    deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
    and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

    \n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

    \n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR
    A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
    WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>


</resources>
